

# Ethan Ling (Yu-Cheng, Ling)

**Database Engineer** 

github (changbiyuan)



+886 910550788



a29286263@gmail.com



Taipei City, Taiwan (R.O.C.)



## **SUMMARY**

I'm Ling Yucheng (Ethan), a recent master's graduate specializing inneural network deep learning with a thesis on Day-to-Night image translationusing GANs. With 2 years of database internship experience and experience inPython, I'm eager to apply my expertise in software development and ML/DL.

## **EDUCATION**

#### National Taipei University of Education

Master of Science in Computer Science 2022 - 2024

#### Shih Hsin University

BS in Information Management 2018 - 2022

## **SKILLS**

- Html
- Css
- Python
- Pytorch
- Oracle Linux
- ODBC
- Git

#### PORTFOLIOS

- High fidelity Day-to-Night Image
  Translation using Global Residual Module
  Generative Adversarial Network. ---
  - Master's Thesis
- Design and Implementation of a Spatiotemporal Air Quality Prediction System Using Geographic Information System (GIS) Techniques. ---Undergraduate Final Project

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Database Assistant Engineer**

Dynasafe | 2022 - Present

- Set up Oracle Database 19c 11g on Linux 7.9 8.0.
- Build high-availability databases with Oracle Database RAC.
- Ensure high availability between RAC instances using Oracle DataGuard.
- Perform database stress testing.
- Extract data from MSSQL and migrate it between tables.
- Implement cross-platform data synchronization using Oracle GoldenGate (Oracle to MSSQL, MSSQL to Oracle).

#### Staff

Uniglo | 2017 - 2022

- Maintained store cleanliness and product presentation, increasing customer shopping willingness.
- Managed inventory to ensure product availability and optimal allocation.
- Provided friendly customer service, addressing inquiries and assisting with shopping needs.
- Actively participated in internal training to enhance product knowledge and service skills.

### OTHERS

- Event General Coordinator of University Graduation Exhibition.
- Outstanding Award in University Graduation Exhibition.

Last Updated: August 29, 2024